Jonas Berglund

Lindholmsallén 25 lgh 116 41753 Gothenburg Sweden

T: +46 703 - 84 67 67

@: berglund.jonas@gmail.com

W: jonasberglund.com

Profile

I have a Bachelor degree in Computer Science and now studying second year at master program in Interaction Design & Technologies at Chalmers University of Technology, Sweden. Recently done an exchange period in Prague, Czech Republic, for half a year. Worked part-time as a consultant in various IT-related projects. During the bachelor education focused in software development and user interaction design. Beside studies worked with iOS development. As a person I am creative, enthusiastic and sociable. I work effectively and finish my assignment within the given time frame with good quality.

Check out my portfolio website at jonasberglund.com

| Education | |
|--|--------------------|
| Master in Interaction Design & Technologies | 2014 - 2016 (exp.) |
| Chalmers University of Technology, Gothenburg | |
| Erasmus exchange student, Information Technology | 2015 |
| Czech Technical University in Prague, Czech Republic | |
| App development for Android | 2014 |
| Summer course at Mittuniversitetet | |
| Development for mobile application | 2014 |
| Summer course at the University of Umeå | |
| | |

Bachelor thesis at Alten, Gothenburg 2014

The thesis was about develop a Cross-platform app for tablets to read document from an encrypted server back end. It comprises the development of using Cordova (PhoneGap) technology together with Intel XDK, as well as an evaluation of Xamarin.

| BSc in Computer Science (180 ECTS) | 2011 - 2014 |
|---|-------------|
| Chalmers University of Technology, Gothenburg | |
| | |
| Multimedia programming in Python | 2013 |
| Multimedia programming in Python | 2013 |

Work experience

Consultant at Chalmers Teknologkonsulter AB

2014 - On-going

IT-consultant, participating in in-house projects and external project for customers (i.e. mobile apps, web apps, and more). The company is totally driven by students, which means I also worked with cold call selling, project meetings and invoicing.

Fitter, Volvo PV, Skövde

2010 - 2011

October 2010 - June 2011

The tasks included the outer assembly of diesel engines. The working hours were rolling shift schedule day, evening and night.

Driver, Posten Logistik

Lindholmsallén 25 lgh 116 41753 Gothenburg

T: +46 703 - 84 67 67
@: berglund.jonas@gmail.com
W: jonasberglund.com

Sweden

2008 - 2012

Summers between 2008 - 2012

Duties were mainly sorting and delivery of packages to the customer, primarily to businesses.

Positions of trust

Board member for the Chalmers alumni association CLC 2014 - On-going

Alumni association for graduated Chalmers students working for good fellowship among its members.

Vice President of the H-section, Chalmers

2013 - 2014

Elected by the section to the Vice President of the H-section, which is the largest section of Chalmers. The work consists of managing the section's statutes and regulations and to be in touch and support the section's committees and compounds, and other regularly board work.

SAMO of the H-section, Chalmers

2013 - 2014

Students' work environment representative (Studerande Arbetsmiljöombud), whose work involves acting for students feeling safe in their learning environment, both physical and psychosocial. The role includes being a link between the students and the student body, as well as program managers' teachers.

Languages

Swedish, native language.

English, fluent in spoken and written.

German, basic knowledge of both spoken and written.

Programming skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Swift, Objective-C, Java, Android, C, C++, Python, PHP, AngularJS, Meteor, XML, SQL, assembly.

SCRUM, Agile, Git, Xcode, Eclipse, ADT.

Additional information

On two different occasions received scholarships of total 20 000 SEK for good study and great commitment to the school's development, in parallel with the studies.

Member of Apple's iOS Developer Program since the spring of 2013 and have released three apps in the App Store. Also, a registered Android Developer, and has released two apps on Google Play, one which was developed during a school project together with classmates.

Have combined full-time study at college engaging in a very active guild committee where my responsibilities have included planning, implementation and follow-up of various events.

41753 Gothenburg Sweden

Lindholmsallén 25 lgh 116

T: +46 703 - 84 67 67

@: berglund.jonas@gmail.com

W: jonasberglund.com

Referrals

Referrals, tests and work certificates are available upon request.